Finding Aid for Vice Provost for Academic and Multicultural Affairs (University of Michigan) records, 1970-2000
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Office Of Academic Multicultural Initiatives, 1987-1997
  - Financial Analysis, 1993 (Box 19)
  - Freshmen Recruitment, 1995 (Box 19)
  - Funding (Requests for), 1990-1993 (Box 19)
  - Funding (Minority Initiatives, 1990-1994 (Box 19)
  - General Files
    - 1990-1994 (Box 19)
    - 1993-1995 (Box 19)
  - Initiatives, 1993-1995 (Box 19)
  - Intergroup Relations Program Office, 1994 (Box 19)
  - John Matlock/Department of Public Safety arrest incident, 1995 (Box 19)
  - Mission, 1990-1991 (Box 19)
  - Policy and Procedure Handbook for Students, 1991-1992 (Box 19)
  - Presentations, 1990-1991 (Box 19)
  - Problems/Issues, 1992-1994 (Box 19)
  - Programming, 1993-1994 (Box 19)
  - Publications, 1988-1993 (Box 19)
  - Recruiting Freshmen, 1987-1992 (Box 19)
  - Resource Center, 1992-1993 (Box 19)
  - Student Leader Development, 1990 (Box 19)
- University of Michigan Schools and Colleges, 1992-1999
  - 1992-1997
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of
      - 1994-1996 (Box 26)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 26)
    - Art, School of
      - 1992-1994 (Box 26)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 26)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 26)
    - Business Administration, School of
      - 1992-1993 (Box 26)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 26)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 26)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 26)
    - Dentistry, School of
      - General
        - 1994-1995 (Box 26)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 26)
      - Multicultural Audit Report, 1995 (Box 26)
    - Education, School of
      - 1994-1996 (Box 26)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 26)
    - Engineering, School of
      - General
        - 1992-1993 (Box 26)
        - 1994-1996 (Box 26)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 26)
      - GEM (National Consortium for Graduate Degrees in Engineering and Science) Mentoring Program, 1995 (Box 26)
      - MEPO (Minority Engineering Program Office)
        - 1993-1995 (Box 26)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 26)
    - Flint Campus, 1996-1997 (Box 26)
    - Information, School of (formerly School of Information and Library Studies)
      - 1992-1994 (Box 26)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 26)
      - 1996 (Box 26)
    - Kinesiology, Division of, 1996-1997 (Box 26)
    - Law, School of
      - 1995-1996 (Box 26)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 26)
    - Literature, Sciences, and the Arts, College of
      - General
        - 1992-1994 (Box 27)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 27)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 27)
      - American Culture
        - 1992-1993 (Box 27)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 27)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 27)
      - Anthropology, 1994-1995 (Box 27)
      - Center for Afroamerican and African Studies (CAAS), 1996-1997 (Box 27)
      - Chemistry, 1996-1997 (Box 27)
      - Communication, 1992-1993 (Box 27)
      - English Composition Board, 1992-1994 (Box 27)
      - English Literature and Languages, 1992 (Box 27)
      - Latina/o Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 27)
      - Mathematics
        - 1993 (Box 27)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 27)
      - Pilot Program, 1996-1997 (Box 27)
      - Psychology
        - 1993-1994 (Box 27)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 27)
      - Residential College, 1996-1997 (Box 27)
      - Sociology
        - 1993-1994 (Box 27)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 27)
      - Women's Studies
        - 1996-1997 (Box 27)
    - Medical School
      - General
        - 1992-1994 (Box 27)
        - 1994-1996, 3 folders (Box 27)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 27)
      - Cultural Audit
        - 1994 (Box 27)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 27)
      - Minority Initiatives, 1994-1995 (Box 27)
    - Music, School of
      - 1987-1992 (Box 27)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 27)
    - Natural Resources, School of
      - 1992-1994 (Box 27)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 27)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 27)
    - Nursing, School of
      - 1992-1993 (Box 27)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 27)
    - Pharmacy, School of
      - 1992-1993 (Box 27)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 27)
    - Public Health, School of
      - 1992-1994 (Box 27)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 27)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 27)
    - Public Policy, School of
      - 1994-1995 (Box 27)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 27)
    - Rackham School of Graduate Studies
      - General
        - 1992-1994 (Box 27)
        - 1994-1996 (Box 27)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 27)
      - Rackham Merit Fellowship Program (Minority Fellowship Program), 1996-1997 (Box 27)
    - Social Work, School of
      - 1992-1994 (Box 27)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 27)
  - 1997-1999
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of, 1998-1999
      - General (Box 36)
        [ER restricted unitl July 1, 2023 ]
      - Restricted (Box 41)
    - Art, School of
      - 1997-1998 (Box 36)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 36)
    - Business Administration, School of, 1997-1998 (Box 36)
    - Dentistry, School of, 1997-1998 (Box 36)
    - Education, School of, 1997-1998 (Box 36)
    - Engineering, School of
      - General
        - 1997-1998 (Box 36)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 36)
      - MEPO (Minority Engineering Program Office)
        - 1997-1998 (Box 36)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 36)
    - Flint Campus, 1997-1998 (Box 36)
    - Kinesiology, Division of
      - General, 1996-1997 (Box 36)
      - Search, 1998 (Box 36)
    - Law, School of
      - 1997-1998 (Box 36)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 36)
    - Literature, Sciences, and the Arts, College of
      - General
        - 1997-1998 (Box 36)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 36)
      - American Culture-Latino Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 36)
      - Biology, 1996-1997 (Box 36)
      - Center for Afroamerican and African Studies (CAAS)
        - 1997-1998 (Box 36)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 36)
      - Chemistry, 1997-1998 (Box 41)
      - Residential College
        - General, 1997-1998 (Box 36)
        - Personnel, 1997-1998 (Box 41)
    - Music, School of
      - 1997-1998
        - General (Box 36)
        - Personnel (Box 41)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 36)
    - Natural Resources, School of, 1997-1998 (Box 36)
    - Nursing, School of
      - 1997-1998 (Box 36)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 41)
    - Public Health, School of, 1998-1999 (Box 36)
    - Rackham School of Graduate Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 36)
    - Social Work, School of, 1997-1998 (Box 36)
- Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT)
  - General
    - 1993-1996, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 36)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 36)
  - American Association for Higher Education (AAHE) Peer Review Project, 1996-1997 (Box 37)
  - Director (Connie Cook), 1993-1997 (Box 41)
  - Faculty Associates Program, 1995 (Box 37)
  - Financial
    - 1995-1996 (Box 37)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 37)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 37)
  - Multicultural Teaching Consortium, 1995-1996 (Box 37)
  - Personnel
    - 1995-1996 (Box 41)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 41)
  - Policy Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 37)
  - Teaching Assistants, 1993-1995 (Box 37)
- Military Officer Education Program
  - General
    - 1991-1992
      - General (Box 37)
      - Meeting Minutes and Agendas (Box 37)
    - 1992-1993
      - General (Box 37)
      - Meeting Minutes and Agendas (Box 37)
    - 1993-1994
      - General (Box 37)
      - Meeting Minutes and Agendas (Box 37)
    - 1994-1995
      - General (Box 37)
      - Meeting Minutes and Agendas (Box 37)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 37)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 37)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 37)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 37)
  - Air Force ROTC
    - 1991-1992 (Box 37)
    - 1992-1993
      - General (Box 37)
      - Faculty/Staff Appointments (Box 42)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 37)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 37)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 37)
    - 1996-1997
      - General (Box 37)
      - Faculty/Staff Appointments (Box 42)
    - 1997-1998
      - General (Box 37)
      - Faculty/Staff Appointments (Box 42)
      - General Newton's Visit (Box 37)
    - Col. Robert G. Christiansen (Box 37)
    - Alfredo D. Lopez Jr. (Box 42)
    - Col. Michael D. Allen (Box 42)
  - Army ROTC
    - 1992-1994 (Box 37)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 37)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 37)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 37)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 37)
  - Navy ROTC
    - 1992-1993 (Box 37)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 37)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 37)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 37)
- Student Academic Services
  - Admissions
    - General
      - 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 37)
      - 1997-2000, 3 folders (Box 37)
    - Advanced Placement, 1997 (Box 38)
    - Affirmative Action, 1997-1998 (Box 38)
    - Budget, 1999-2000 (Box 38)
    - Carl Cohen, 1996 (Box 38)
    - Code Implementation Review Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 38)
    - College Level Equivalent Course Directory, 1997 (Box 38)
    - Director (Ted Spencer), 1996-1997 (Box 38)
    - Enrollment Data
      - 1998-1999 (Box 38)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 38)
    - General Counsel, 1996-1999 (Box 42)
    - Legacies Issue, 1991-1992 (Box 38)
    - Meeting with Legislators, 1997 (Box 38)
    - Parents' Complaints, 1998-2000
      - General (Box 38)
      - Restricted (Box 42)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2075 ]
    - Personnel Issues, 1997-1998 (Box 42)
    - Processing, 1997-1998 (Box 38)
    - Recruiting Issues, 1997-1998 (Box 38)
  - Financial Aid
    - General, 1996-1998; 2 folders (Box 38)
    - General Counsel, 1997-1998 (Box 42)
    - Personnel, 1997 (Box 42)
    - Students, 1998 (Box 42)
    - Supplemental Education Opportunity Grant (SEOG), 1996-1997 (Box 38)
  - Office of New Student Programs (ONSP)
    - General
      - 1995-1998, 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Director (Penni Reed), 1995-1997; 2 folders (Box 42)
      - Financial, 1994-1997 (Box 38)
      - Personnel, 1996-1997 (Box 42)
    - Mentorship, 1995-1997 (Box 38)
    - Orientation
      - 1990-1991 (Box 39)
      - 1995 (Box 39)
      - 1996 (Box 39)
    - Welcome to Michigan, 1993-1997 (Box 39)
  - Registrar
    - General
      - 1992-1995 (Box 39)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 39)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 39)
    - Hold Credits, 1992-1995 (Box 39)
- Faculty Awards for Research and Creative Projects (FARCP)
  - 1996
    - Boyd, E. (Box 39)
    - Cameron, J. (Box 39)
    - Coronil, F. (Box 39)
    - Gong, Siew-Ging (Box 39)
    - Lee, S. (Box 39)
    - Majumbar, S. (Box 39)
    - McDaniel, L. (Box 39)
    - Moss, T. (Box 39)
    - Roubidoux, M. (Box 39)
    - Saavedra, R. (Box 39)
    - Sanchez, G. (Box 39)
    - Williams, D. (Box 39)
    - Wilson, R. (Box 39)
    - Wu, M. (Box 39)
    - Research and Creative Projects in the Humanities (Box 39)
  - 1996-1997
    - General (Box 39)
    - Aparicio, F. (Box 39)
    - Ching, Yau (Box 39)
    - Fetters, Michael (Box 39)
    - McGovern, P. (Box 39)
    - O'Connor, Kathleen Malone (Box 39)
    - Pedraza, S. (Box 39)
    - Porter, C. (Box 39)
    - Porter, M. (Box 39)
    - Simpson, R. (Box 39)
  - 1997-1998
    - General, Spring 1997 (Box 39)
    - General, Fall 1997 (Box 39)
    - Faculty Awards Marketing and Guidelines Revision (Box 39)
    - Faculty Awards Summary Reports (Box 39)
    - Lin, Ann (Box 39)
    - Majumdar, S. (Box 39)
    - Nori, F. (Box 39)
    - Owusu, Maxwell (Box 39)
    - Quarcoopome, N. (Box 39)
    - Velez-Aguayo, E. (Box 39)
    - Wagaw, T. (Box 39)
    - Betz, A. Lorris (Box 39)
    - Bonilla-Silva, E. (Box 39)
    - Chhibber, Pradeep (Box 39)
    - Hollingsworth, L. (Box 39)
    - Inuzuka, Sadashi (Box 39)
    - Lam, Joseph (Box 40)
    - Rodemer, Michael (Box 40)
    - Taylor, Stephanie (Box 40)
    - Ching, Yau (Box 40)
    - Dandekar, H. (Box 40)
    - Duanmu, San (Box 40)
    - Epstein, Terrie (Box 40)
    - Gutierrez, L. (Box 40)
    - Heath, Jeffrey (Box 40)
    - Ingersoll-Dayton, Berit (Box 40)
    - Kasa-Vubu, Josephine (Box 40)
    - Killion, Cheryl (Box 40)
    - Lauffer, Armand (Box 40)
    - Naomi, Andre (Box 40)
    - Reed, Beth G., 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Smith, Sidonie (Box 40)
    - Walwyn, Karen (Box 40)
    - West, Edward (Box 40)
    - Yeo, SeonAe (Box 40)
    - Aparicio, F. (Box 40)
    - Allen, R. (Box 40)
    - Chen, Z. (Box 40)
    - Duanmu, San (Box 40)
    - Ekotto, F. (Box 40)
    - Gikandi, S. (Box 40)
    - Gitelman, Z. (Box 40)
    - Gocek, F. (Box 40)
    - Gonzalez, J. (Box 40)
    - Ingersoll-Dayton, Berit (Box 40)
  - Bobo, L./Lempert-Presidential Professor, 1994-1996 (Box 40)